Guide to the United Automobile Workers of America, District 65 Photographs, Part I: Negatives PHOTOS.023
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archive
- Series I. Negatives, Bulk, 1940-1959; 1938-1969 (bulk 1940s-1950s)
  - Subseries I:D - Meetings and Events - 1938-1969
    - Social Service: Local 19; Strike Committee; Workers Meeting, Mar 27, 1951; Jan 19, 1952; Jan 14, 1951 (Negative 7685; 8413 - 8414; 7489 - 7491)
    - Solumbe Co. Back Pay, Aug 22, 1950 (Negative 7065)
    - South Bronx Stewards Meet, Sep 1963 (Negative 22485 - 22487)
    - Spanish Labor Symposium, May 4, 1958 (Negative 25281 - 25308)
    - Spanish Membership: Meetings Includes (M.M.P. Local), Apr 25, 1952; Oct 27, 1954; Mar 23, 1954 (Negative 8714 - 8719; 13466; 12703)
    - Spanish Speaking: Committee - Rank and File; Meeting; Spanish-Speaking 65 Officers Meet on Discrimination Problems; Membership Meeting; Spanish-Speaking Organizer, Apr 1942; Nov 19, 1953; Dec 17, 1959; Jul 29, 1953; Aug 24, 1953 (Negative 1066; 12035 - 12041; 17775 - 17777; 11426 - 11427; 11597 - 11598)
    - Special Stewards Meeting With David Livingston, Dec 30, 1957 (Negative 16306 - 16308)
    - Spiegel Novelty Shop Meets On Contract, Jan 27, 1959 (Negative 17053 - 17061)
    - Sponcraft Ratifies Shop Meeting, May 25, 1953 (Negative 11424)
    - Square Furniture Committee, Jun 28, 1961 (Negative 19119)
    - Stallo Manufacturing Co., Mar 20, 1958 (Negative 16442)
    - Standard Bias and Binding Co. Shop, Nov 1, 1956 (Negative 15504)
    - Standard Corrugated Shop Meeting, May 17, 1962 (Negative 20162 - 20165)
    - Standard Sample Card - Ratification: Workers Re-elect Connie Thomas; Crews 52 + 58, Mar 4, 1943; Feb 14, 1956; Aug 2, 1950 (Negative 1383 - 1384; 14632; 7020)
    - Standard Scientific Corp.: Newly-Organized Shop, Feb 2, 1961 (Negative 18630)
    - Star Casting Inc. Meeting, Jul 29, 1955 (Negative 14267)
    - Star Suspender Election, Jul 24, 1945 (Negative 2227)
    - Star Tag and Label: Newly-Organized Shop, Oct 14, 1957 (Negative 16149)
    - State CIO Convention Held at Long Beach, Sep 24, 1953 (Negative 11701 - 11708)
    - Steel Slides Inc. Organization, Sep 7, 1961 (Negative 19285 - 19286)
    - Steel Strike Aid: from Stern Store [local]; from Hearns [local], 1952; Jul 18, 1952 (Negative 9181; 9208 - 9209)
    - Stein Children Get Money Raised in RTV in Honor of Late Father Milton Stein, Apr 5, 1959 (Negative 17204 - 17205)
    - Stephen Rug Mills Shop Meeting, May 25, 1950 (Negative 6699 - 6699)
    - Sterling Sign, Nov 24, 1940 (Negative 385)
    - Stern's: 1954 Contract Ratification; Negotiations; Office; Office Crew Meeting; Stern's Paramus Polio Shots; Rank and Filers; Ratification; Shoe Department Meeting, Oct 18, 1955; Nov 22, 1955; Apr 25, 1956; Jan 28, 1957; Sep 22, 1953; Apr 2, 1957; Jun 28, 1961; Jul 21, 1954; Sep 11, 1956; Dec 17, 1957; May 17, 1955 (Negative 14404; 14458 - 14461; 14964; 15642 - 15643; 11696 - 11697; 15863; 19110 - 19118; 13246 - 13249; 15330 - 15333; 16301; 14115)
    - Stern (con't): Strike Committee Meets to Plan for 1958 Contract Expiration; Warehouse Meetings; Warehouse Steward Election; Workers Joseph De Matteo and Co.; Watches, Mar 26, 1952; May 16, 1959; Sep 24, 1957; Apr 28, 1962; Feb 15, 1953; Apr 30, 1957; Jan 4, 1956; Feb 8, 1961; Jan 26, 1956; Nov 5, 1954; Nov 10, 1948; 1939 (Negative 8596 - 8597; 17446 - 17449; 16126; 20102 - 20105; 9832 - 9832; 15890; 14546; 18668 - 18669; 14589 - 14590; 13500; 4673 - 4674; 46)
    - Stern's: Executive Meeting; (B-2) Meeting; Conference; Election Petrie Stores; Meetings; Sign for Class; Taking Pledge; Front View of Stern's Building; Stern and Klaber Bros Bulletin Boards; Beauty Shop; (3rd Floor Crew) Steward Election, 1940-1962 (Negative 859; 148; 22526 - 22557; 19314; 1163 - 1165; 8538 - 8540; 584; 19456 - 19457; 1369; 20123 - 20126; 8140 - 8144; 9481; 12613; 12892; 4635 - 4635; 6374 - 6383; 6381; 3173; 4482; 5133 - 5134; 6678;)
    - Stern's (con't): Executive Board; Election; Election Victory; Grievance Committees; Local 5 Meetings; Meetings; Meetings at Hotel Diplomat; Meeting on Secession; Membership Meetings; Membership Meeting on Compliance; Officers; Organizers Christmas Tree on 7th Floor, Nov 22, 1948; Mar 22, 1949; Sep 23, 1952; Jun 22, 1949; Jun 22, 1949; Sep 21, 1948; Aug 16, 1949; Apr 29, 1953; Apr 30, 1952; Sep 29, 1948; Nov 16, 1948; Dec 18, 1952; 1951; Jan 17, 1952; Mar 11, 1953; Jan 29, 1957; Apr 20, 1955; Sep 30, 1953; Oct 1, 1957 (Negative '4682 - 4685; 4983; 9453 - 9455; 5285 - 5285; 5286 - 5287; 4498 - 4499; 5423 - 5426; 10704; 8734 - 8737; 4524 - 4529; 4670 - 4672; 10106 - 10107; 8017; 8395 - 8396; 10291; 15644; 14027; 11752; 16138)
    - Stern's (con't): Vote Union Shop; Local 5 Executive Board; Restaurant Workers; Arbitration of 56 Reopener; Crew Elections; Employees Ratify Terms of New Two-Year Settlement at Hotel Diplomat; Executive Board; Executive Board Local 5; Local 5 Meeting, Mar 12, 1956; Oct 14, 1953; Feb 28, 1956; Aug 14, 1951; Sep 17, 1956; Jul 21, 1953; Sep 22, 1954; Apr 21, 1953; Feb 2, 1949; Sep 14, 1955; Oct 5, 1949; Sep 14, 1949; May 21, 1952; Mar 1, 1955; Aug 24, 1955 (Negative 14711 - 14713; 11844 - 11845; 16406 - 16413; 7886; 15340; 11372 - 11373; 13396; 10669; 4850 - 4851; 14344; 5583 - 5587; 5504 - 5506; 8995 - 9010; 13849 - 13850; 14314 - 14317)
    - Steward Buttons, Copy of, Jan 18, 1954 (Negative 12324)
    - Stickless Corp: Newly-Organized Shop; Workers Ratify First District 65 Contract, Jan 26, 1956; Sep 10, 1956 (Negative 14592; 15325)
    - Stonehill Labs: Meetings; Newly-Organized, Sep 29, 1954; Nov 12, 1956 (Negative 13493 - 13494; 15522)
    - Stop Work Meeting, Mar 24, 1965 (Negative 23846 - 23861)
    - Store Workers: General Council Meeting, Dec 12, 1962; Aug 30, 1950; Oct 17, 1956; Feb 20, 1962 (Negative 21022-21029; 7086 - 7089; 15474; 19821 - 19822)
    - Strauss Stores: Election Ballot Count; Negotiating Committee; Pre-Election Meeting; Strauss Store in Brooklyn Showing Posted A.F.L. Leaflets; Warehouse [Meeting], Aug 1951; Jan 29, 1952; Mar 26, 1953; Feb 10, 1953; Feb 12, 1953; Nov 13, 1952 (Negative 7894; 8464; 10580 - 10585; 9801 - 9802; 9793 - 9798; 9939;)
    - Straw Vote at Dry Goods Meeting, Sep 20, 1945 (Negative 2300)
    - Strike Bulletin, Jan 31, 1957 (Negative 15645 - 15654)
    - Strike Committee (Davega, Miles, Beck), Jan 17, 1952 (Negative 8397 - 8398)
    - Strike Vote - Davega and Shoe, 1952 (Negative 8419 - 8425)
    - Stunzi Ratification, Aug 17, 1942 (Negative 1227)
    - Stuyvesant Area Strike Committee, Jan 10, 1952 (Negative 8305 - 8306)
    - Style Rite Optical: Newly-Organized Shop; Workers Win First Contract Under District 65 (Swearing-In); Strike Fund; Meetings; Workers Celebrate NLRB Elections Victory, Jun 24, 1957; Jul 8, 1957; undated; Aug 28, 1961; Oct 20, 1959 (Negative 16003 - 16010; 16032 - 16034; 25809 - 25811; 19227 - 19228; 17699 - 17701)
    - Stylecraft Hosiery, Aug 10, 1953 (Negative 11455 - 11456)
    - Subscription Service of District 65, Mar 10, 1954 (Negative 12614)
    - Sunshine Nov. SLRB [New York State Labor Relations Board ?] Vote, Mar 31, 1942 (Negative 1058)
    - Supply Sales, Dec 14, 1955 (Negative 14512)
    - Suspender: Suspender and Garter Shops Ratify 1954 Contract; Membership Meeting; Shops; Wage Committee; Suspender-Garter Association, Feb 25, 1954; Sep 22, 1953; Oct 29, 1954; Dec 7, 1953; Dec 10, 1953 (Negative 12552; 11695; 13470 - 13471; 12172; 12177)
    - Sweepstakes Winner Harry Dyckoff, Mar 30, 1950 (Negative 6472 - 6475)
    - Tattula Shop - Dicker, Dec 10, 1951 (Negative 8211)
    - Tavrone Label Shop Meeting, Nov 27, 1956 (Negative 15559)
    - TBX Pays at District 65, Feb 17, 1947 (Negative 2983 - 2984)
    - Teddy's Sea Food: Newly-Organized Shop, Oct 14, 1957 (Negative 16150)
    - Test Shots, Feb 26-27,1941 (Negative 565 - 566)
    - Textile (I): Arbitration - First Hearing; Arbitration Meeting; Association 65ers Ratify New 2-year Pact on Eve of Deadline; Association Ratification; Association Ratifies; Banquet; Banquet Committee; Committees; Crew 37; Crew Election; Crews; Crews # 12, 13, 20, and 21; Crews 469-7th Avenue, 1410 Broadway, 1412 Broadway, and 1441 Broadway, Jan 29, 1952; Apr 28, 1962; Jan 6, 1954; Apr 14, 1959; Mar 19, 1957; Oct 1, 1946; Agu 22, 1946; Jan 8, 1941; Mar 24, 1942; Apr 8, 1941; Apr 30, 1957; Jun 1, 1953; Mar 11, 1954; Feb 13, 1954; Dec 17, 1952; Jan 27, 1953 (Negative 8463; 20106 - 20108; 12280 - 12281; 17259; 15842; 2842 - 2846; 2792; 892; 1049; 625 - 627; 15889; 11034 - 11035; 12624 - 12625)
    - Textile (II): (con't)Crews Elect Stewards #33, Lonchamps Rose Harbor Du Barry, Decision; Emergency Meeting; Executive Board Meetings; Executive Board; Fabric; General Council; Local Meets to Act on May First 1959 Contract Offer; Local Ratifies New Contract; Meetings; Member-[Who Is A] Stringer for Radio Station Wins Charles [sic?] Sarnoff [Award?], Oct 29, 1953; Sep 22, 1954; Apr 1, 1957; Jan 7, 1957; Jan 13, 1954; Oct 29, 1953; Sep 22, 1954; Apr 1, 1957; Jan 7, 1957; Jan 13, 1954; Jan 7, 1954; Sep 13, 1956; Feb 18, 1954; Aug 14, 1957; May 13, 1942 (Negative 12451 - 12459; 10093; 9752; 11891; 13359; 15861; 15616; 12301; 12285 - 12286; 15338 - 15339; 12532 - 12533; 16080; 1097-1098; 15315 - 15316; 5148; 11317; 13403; 13822; 11145; 12869 - 12870; 17263)
    - Textile (III): (con't) Members Welcome New Worker to Market; Membership Meetings; Swearing in Cohn-Hall-Marx Workers; Elections; Office Workers Membership Meeting; Organizing Committee; Organizing Meeting; Ratification; Ratification Meeting; Stewards, Aug 28, 1956; May 17, 1949; Jul 15, 1953; Sep 30, 1954; Feb 9, 1955; Jun 23, 1953; May 4, 1954; Apr 16, 1959; Apr 30, 1959; Jun 11, 1943; 1967; Apr 1967; Mar 5, 1959; Mar 5, 1959; Oct 20, 1953; Jul 20, 1954 (Negative 17277 - 17278; 1495; 24443 - 24453; 25226; 17166 - 17167; 17151 - 17163; 11852 - 11853; 13242; 13414 - 13415)
    - Textile (IV): (con't) Stewards Meet on Contract Offer; Stewards Receive Watches for 100% Attendance at Meetings; Strike Meeting; Workers Vote Strike; Israel Trip Raffle At Textile Meeting; Special Textile Executive Board Meeting; "V" Board, Oct 12, 1954; Nov 16, 1954; Aug 16, 1955; Oct 11, 1955; Dec 13, 1955; Feb 17, 1959; Jan 19, 1953; Apr 18, 1961; May 21, 1968; Jun 26, 1958; May 28, 1956; Aug 23, 1960; Apr 23, 1957 (Negative 13530 - 13532; 14301 - 14303; 14380 - 14381; 14511; 17124; 9725; 18819 - 18823; 25276 - 25280; 16622 - 16625; 15155; 18227; 15877)
    - Theatre Tickets Booth, Nov 6, 1952 (Negative 9895)
    - Theon Manufacturing: Newly-Organized; Shop Meeting, Aug 23, 1960; Sep 27, 1960 (Negative 18228 - 18229; 18298)
    - Three Men with Movie Projector (ca. 1939-1940) (Negative 29661)
    - Times Square [Stores] Ballot Box, Jul 6, 1948 (Negative 4356)
    - Title Guaranty and Trust Co.: Committee; Stewards, Jan 5, 1954; May 14, 1957; 1951 (Negative 12275; 15941; 7493)
    - Top Value Dist. Shop Meeting, Oct 16, 1961 (Negative 19359)
    - Towns and James: Salesmen Meet During Strike; Salesmen Vote to Strike, May 1960; Mar 31, 1960 (Negative 18178; 18021)
    - Toy and Gift: Executive Board; Executive Board Meet with Manhattan Novelty Strikers; Executive Board Meetings; Membership; Membership Meeting; 'Toy and Gift Membership Meeting - Representatives of Democratic and Republican Parties Speak; 'Toy Association Shops; 'Toy-Giftware Shop Meeting [Zader-Feldstein Shop?], Dec 6, 1956; May 12, 1958; Sep 10, 1956; Oct 8, 1953; Dec 13, 1954; May 1954; Oct 18, 1956; Jul 28, 1954; Jan 24, 1954 (Negative 15591; 16552; 15329; 11781 - 11783; 13664; 12906; 15477; 13263; 29901)
    - Trans-American Trade Corp.: Newly-Organized Shop, Sep 16, 1957 (Negative 16109)
    - Transcontinental Tool Shop, Nov 1, 1955 (Negative 14422)
    - Transpar Co.: Newly-Organized Shop, Aug 23, 1957 (Negative 16091)
    - U.S. Announcement Card 7-0 Vote for District 65, 1951 (Negative 7633)
    - U.S. Chemical: Meeting, Nov 1962; Dec 13, 1956 (Negative 20941 - 20944; 15597)
    - U.S. Tool Co. - Newly-Organized Shop, Feb 20, 1958 (Negative 16373)
    - U-1 and U-3 (Uptown Sections 1 and 3): Meetings (Mac Mattis); Unification, Oct 21, 1940; Oct 1942 (Negative 29658 - 29659; 1286)
    - U-2 (Uptown Section 2): Garment Membership Meeting; Stewards, Jul 16, 1953; Aug 12, 1941 (Negative 11334; 714)
    - U-4 (Uptown Section 4): Stewards; Executive Board; Executive Board Cosmetics and Drugs, Feb 6, 1941; Jun 2, 1953; Jan 14, 1953 (Negative 520; 11051 - 11052; 9701)
    - U-5 (Uptown Section 5): Membership Meeting; Stewards, Apr 29, 1942; Jul 1942 (Negative 1067 - 1068; 1197)
    - Unemployment: Unemployed 65ers Learn New Skills in Direct Mail Industry; Unemployed Meetings; Unemployed Sign Cards for Unemployment Insurance; Unemployment and Committee Meeting, May 20, 1958; Nov 11, 1941; Mar 9, 1959; Feb 15, 1949; Apr 7, 1940 (Negative 16537 - 16541; 810; 17092 - 17093; 4877; 29694)
    - Unidentified Convention or Meetings: ca. 1940s? (Includes Shots of Arthur Osman, Transport Workers Union President Michael Quill Speaking, and a Photographer); ca. 1939?, undated; Nov 28, 1947; undated; Sep 6, 1946; undated; undated; undated; undated; Feb 6, 1959; 1955; May 15, 1956; 1968 (Negative 13855 - 13863; 13866 - 13882; 14173 - 14180; 3219-3219; 14180 - 14188; 14195; 25693; 25821 - 25823; 25824 - 25826; 18225; 17097; 13892 - 13901; 15143; 29616 - 29621)
    - Union News Company: Meetings; Negotiating Committee; Negotiations and Strike Preparation; Shop Meetings, Nov 30, 1952; Jun 4, 1953; Feb 17, 1954; Dec 14, 1950; 1951; Jul 27, 1953; Jun 9, 1955; Dec 14, 1959; Sep 30, 1957; Dec 18, 1952; May 28, 1953 (Negative 10012 - 10015; 11067 - 11069; 12538 - 12538; 7419 - 7420; 7496 - 7498; 11411 - 11412; 14321 - 14322; 17768 - 17770; 16129 - 16135; 10105; 11026 - 11027)
    - Union Officers Leaving Jail, Apr 3, 1952 (Negative 8644 - 8648)
    - Union Wide Manhattan Center Meeting, Apr 5, 1948 (Negative 3597 - 3599)
    - United Retail and Wholesale Emplyees of America (URWEA): Second International Convention; Speakers on Dais, 1940; 1940 (Negative 66 - 67; 68 - 73)
    - Unorganized Shop, Jun 22, 1950 (Negative 6947)
    - Uptown Section Meeting, Manhattan Center, Dec 3, 1940 (Negative 248 - 249)
    - Uptown Textile Meeting: Vito Marcantonio and Esther Letz; Converter Ratification, Oct 7, 1947; Dec 18, 1940 (Negative 3153 - 3154; 241 - 242)
    - Used Car Lot - [Credit Union feature], Sep 15, 1952 (Negative 9429)
    - Vacation Feature: 3rd Week Vacations for Union Members Employed In Department Stores, Dec 31, 1953 (Negative 12258 - 12261)
    - Van Iderstine: Local 121; Negotiating Committees; Negotiating Committee at Plant After Pact Victory; Shop Meetings, Nov 1949; Jan 13, 1957; Oct 28, 1957; Nov 13, 1959; Nov 30, 1952; Nov 2, 1959 (Negative 29571; 15622; 16245 - 16247; 17723 - 17725; 10007 - 10011; 17707)
    - Variety Group: Joint Meeting With UOPWA (United Office and Professional Workers of America) Group, 1950; Aug 2, 1950; Sep 14, 1950 (Negative 7051 - 7052; 7029 - 7030; 7110)
    - Vatco Label Meeting, Nov 3, 1952 (Negative 9883)
    - Vets Get Bonus Forms Notarized, Jan 7, 1948 (Negative 3494)
    - Veulf, Mary (Lerners), Sep 15, 1949 (Negative 5507)
    - Vico: Maintenance; Ratification, 1953; 1961 (Negative 11605; 19450 - 19451)
    - Vicron Workers, Mar 5, 1963 (Negative 21263 - 21266)
    - Victory Committee - Tin Foil Donation, Mar 1942 (Negative 1012)
    - Vim (Chain): Meetings; Office Workers; Ratify Laico Settlement; Committee Meeting; Employers; Mediation; Negotiating Committee; Ratification Meeting; Steward; Stewards Meeting; Stewards Prepare Strike Signs; Strike Vote; Warehouse - Office Meeting, Apr 13, 1954; Sep 20, 1954; Feb 23, 1954; Dec 2, 1954; Oct 10, 1952; Dec 1949; May 6, 1964; 1951; Aug 25, 1950; Oct 2, 1950; Jan 1950; Oct 17, 1949; Oct 5, 1954; Mar 30, 1961; Apr 30, 1953 (Negative 12804; 13393; 12528; 13614 - 13615; 9546; 5838; 23181 - 23186; 8139; 7077; 7132 - 7133; 6071; 5654; 13410 - 13411; 18831; 10721)
    - Vineland Committee Meets with President Livingston, Aug 28, 1956 (Negative 15317)
    - Visiting Committee, Jan 14, 1952 (Negative 8363 - 8363)
    - Vita Foods: First Contract Ratification; Negotiating Committee; Shop Meetings; Shop Meets on Possible Strike; Memberships; Committee; Strikers Ratify Strike Settlement, Jun 11, 1953; Sep 27, 1954; Jun 4, 1953; Mar 13, 1956; Apr 29, 1959; Apr 28, 1954; Jun 2, 1954; Nov 3, 1952; Nov 24, 1953; May 23, 1953; Jun 26, 1959; Oct 14, 1952 (Negative 11090 - 11091; 13491 - 13492; 11070 - 11071; 14714; 17272 - 17273; 12855; 13048; 9882; 12069 - 12070; 10328; 17424 - 17427; 9560 - 9563)
    - Vitamin Quota: Meeting; Committee; Quota Shop, Jun 15, 1962; Dec 3, 1952; Nov 14, 1952 (Negative 20795 - 20796; 10038 - 10042; 9954)
    - Volunteer Office Workers, 4th floor, Jul 1949 (Negative 5330)
    - Voting 1964 - June, Bobby Berse in Repose, Jun 1964 (Negative 23280 - 23289)
    - W. L. Blumberg: Shop Meeting; Workers Ratify 1955 Contract, Oct 4, 1954; Oct 28, 1953; Jun 14, 1955 (Negative 13408; 12242; 14196)
    - Wachtel Contract, Nov 9, 1940 (Negative 380)
    - Wage Discussion Headquarters [sic] AM SPL ST, Jul 23, 1951 (Negative 7786 - 7787)
    - Wanamaker Building District 65 Neighborhood Razed By Fire, Jul 16, 1956 (Negative 15231 - 15234)
    - Warehouse Conference, Nov 8, 1961 (Negative 19458 - 19460)
    - Washington March, Robinson Receives Check Proceeds of Long Island Party, Sep 1963 (Negative 22409)
    - Weatherall Prod Co. Meeting, Johnny Mongello Speaking, Oct 17, 1950 (Negative 7255)
    - Weinstock Bros. - Back Paycheck, Feb 10, 1941 (Negative 527)
    - Weiss - Osman Rally, Feb 28, 1940 (Negative 175 - 177)
    - Welfare Committee: Hernia Campaign, May 8, 1944 (Negative 1749)
    - Weltex Woolens Shop Meeting [?], Jul 28, 1955 (Negative 14261 - 14264)
    - Wertheimer: Notice to Workers from Union Negotiating Committee (Department Store and Warehouse Employees Union Local 1499); Store With Anti-Union Sign; Window Display, Feb 19, 1951; Dec 6, 1950; Jun 29, 1950; Oct 13, 1960 (Negative 7599 - 7600; 7431; 6953 - 6954; 18301)
    - Westinghouse Workers Presented With Check for $1000 to Assist Strike (Received by Paul Jennings Sec. Treas. IEU-CIO), Nov 28, 1955 (Negative 14467)
    - Whelan: Heads; NLRB Election; Whelan-Liggett Arbitration, Apr 28, 1943; Apr 28, 1943; 1950 (Negative 1415 - 1418; 1419; 7044 - 7045)
    - Wholesale Shoe Market Contract Meeting, Mar 11, 1954 (Negative 12638 - 12641)
    - Willoughby Camera: Ratifies New Pact; Store Front; Store Workers Celebrate Election Victory, Jul 10, 1959; Jul 1963; Mar 11, 1957 (Negative 17452 - 17453; 21980 - 21981; 15828 - 15831)
    - Willow and Linwood Textile - Newly-Organized Swearing-In, Aug 21, 1958 (Negative 16666)
    - Wilness Mfg.: Wilness Membership, Sep 2, 1958; Apr 27, 1953; Jun 16, 1954; May 13, 1953; Jan 12, 1959 (Negative 16669; 10679 - 10680; 13136; 10894 - 10895; 17042)
    - Winthrop Products Workers Elect New Stewards, Sep 20, 1956 (Negative 15350)
    - Wishnetsky Strikers: Copies of Backup Checks; Copy Pg. 1; Copy Pg. 2, Mar 27, 1941; Mar 29, 1941; Mar 31, 1941; May 7, 1941; Jan 18, 1941; Jan 18, 1941 (Negative 594; 596; 609 - 610; 676; 452; 453)
    - Wiz Ratification, Sep 6, 1941 (Negative 746)
    - Women in Corrugated: Meeting, Jun 5, 1961 (Negative 19074)
    - Woolen: Association; Shops; Shops Prepare 1957 Negotiations; Negotiating Committee, Dec 9, 1955; Apr 29, 1954; Dec 11, 1956; May 16, 1955 (Negative 13652; 12860 - 12861; 15595; 14091 - 14092)
    - Woolworth: Arbitration Award; At Conciliation; At NLRB; Election; Map Campaign; Meetings; Negotiation Committee; Meeting after Election; Strike Vote; App. Card; Meetings, Aug 22, 1946; Sep 19, 1946; Aug 3, 1946; Jul 6, 1944; Jan 1943; Jul 9, 1946; Dec 5, 1941; Jan 1943; Jun 27, 1944; Aug 1944; Jan 1943; Jul 30, 1946; Mar 22, 1946; Mar 15, 1944 (Negative 2782 - 2783; 2835 - 2837; 2765 - 2766; 1867 - 1868; 1361 - 1362; 2718; 851 - 854; 1339 - 1341; 1861 - 1863; 1904; 1363; 2762 - 2763; 2555; 1637 - 1638)
    - World Mose Co.: Newly-Organized Shop, Jun 27, 1957 (Negative 16041)
    - World Warehouse: District 65ers on New Job; Oldtimers (National Mallison), Mar 24, 1953; Feb 17, 1953 (Negative 10323 - 10327; 10179 - 10180)
    - World Wide Shop Meeting, Mar 27, 1951 (Negative 7688 - 7689)
    - Yorkville Medical Group, Aug 24, 1954 (Negative 13327 - 13332)
    - Youth Group Speaker Iris Adams Baum at 2/27/60, General Council, Feb 27, 1960 (Negative 17975)
    - Zadek - Feldstein Shop Meeting, Dec 28, 1953 (Negative 12241)
    - Zelart Meeting, Apr 21, 1950 (Negative 6545)
    - Zell-Meeting, Oct 22, 1945 (Negative 2366)
    - Zipper Hospital: District 65 Wins First Pact [for], Jun 18, 1956 (Negative 15202)
    - Zylite Optical Settles 2/1/58 Contract, Jan 21, 1958 (Negative 16319)
  - Subseries I:E - Members at Home - 1946-1968
    - Arrow Metal Workers at Home, for Negro History Exhibit, Feb 3, 1951 (Negative 7527 - 7532)
    - Baron Family, Oct 3, 1962 (Negative 20550 - 20553)
    - Bauling, Leon ["Portrait" Feature], Apr 17, 1950 (Negative 28687)
    - Calvasa, Ralph [Namm Worker], and Family at Home, Dec 11, 1947 (Negative 3437 - 3441)
    - Davila Family, Jan 1964 (Negative 22878 - 22881)
    - Dolgin, Morris, Jan 12, 1961 (Negative 29585 - 29588)
    - Feller, Harriet and Bernice, Twins, with Boy Friends, Sep 29, 1948 (Negative 29567 - 29568)
    - Gabrera Children and Godmother, Aug 3, 1948 (Negative 29565)
    - Gayron Family, Department Store Wages, Aug 29, 1950 (Negative 29574 - 29576)
    - Gonzalez, Juan Vega of Vita Foods: Union Helped Get Him a New Home After Fire; Gonzalez Family, in New Home after Fire, Apr 6, 1964 (Negative 23169; 23172 - 23174)
    - Hoffman, Virginia ["Portrait" feature], Dec 13, 1959 (Negative 29180 - 29182)
    - Interview Feature, Metal Local Steward Bernie Szczeanski, Jan 11, 1961 (Negative 18602 - 18605)
    - Kemp, Ruth, and Family, Oct 1964 (Negative 23573 - 23575)
    - Kornhaber Triplets at 2 months, 5 months, 6 months, 7 months, 8 months, 10 months, 1 Year., Jun 6, 1946; Jul 27, 1946; Aug 24, 1946; Oct 6, 1946; Oct 11, 1946; Dec 28, 1946, Feb 15, 1947 (Negative 29531 - 29532; 29533 - 29534; 29539 - 29540; 29542; 28558; 29544 - 29545; 29550)
    - Kramer Family, Sep 29, 1962 (Negative 20525 - 20532)
    - Local 26, Distributive, Processing and Office Workers of America, of Suffolk, Virginia: Members at Home and in Town, Sep 21, 1952 (Negative 9463 - 9468)
    - Medical Plan Community Meeting in B'kln Zones 23,24,29,35,13,25,33; Medical Plan Community Meeting of Bensonhurst Held at the Home of Organizer, P. Montanaro, Plus Harlem, Washington Heights, Queens; Medical Plan, South Bronx Community Party Held at Home of Cintron, Louis, Sep 1953; Jan 13, 1954; Jul 17, 1954 (Negative 11680; 12302 - 12310; 13232 - 13239)
    - Michell, Thomas, and Family, Feb 13, 1961 (Negative 18665 - 18667)
    - Morales Family's Second Set of Twins, undated (Negative 24432 - 24434)
    - Nelson, Lilo, Bloomingdale Worker: Exhibition of Ceramics at Home, Nov 1967 (Negative 25110 - 25112)
    - Neuberger, Walter, at Home, Sep 1964 (Negative 23372 - 23377)
    - Nieva Family, Jan 1964 (Negative 23023 - 23024)
    - Pasternak, Mark ["Portrait" Feature], undated (Negative 29337 - 29340)
    - Pioret, Juditte, and sons, Jonathan and Jasper, Dec 1966 (Negative 24546 - 24547)
    - Puglisi, Sal, and Family, Aug 1950 (Negative 29572 - 29573)
    - Rissmeyer, Mother Joy, of Gimbels - Valley Stream, May 1963 (Negative 21692 - 21695)
    - Rodriguez Family at Scene of Fire, Feb 1963 (Negative 21206 - 21212)
    - Rodriguez House: Kids Play in Street, Jul 18, 1953; Aug 13, 1953; Sep 26, 1953 (Negative 11341 - 11342; 11343 - 11351; 11352 - 11356)
    - Rodriguez, Raphael, Family Interview, May 3, 1961 (Negative 18885 - 18889)
    - Roman, Miguel; Apartment after Kerosene Fire, Feb 12, 1955 (Negative 13804 - 13810)